kwiclick.com 2010-11-24

# Privacy Policy - KwiClick

  * 1\. Information Collection & Use
  * 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * 3\. Legal Disclaimer
  * 4\. Security
  * 5\. Contact Us

## 1\. Information Collection & Use

We are committed to protecting online users privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below.

### 1.1 Registration

KwiClick does not collect ANY personal information when you use the KwiClick browser extension.

### 1.2 Children's Privacy Policy

KwiClick is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through our web site.

### 1.3 Profile

We do not store information using client-side cookies or server-side log files of your preferences. Information that you enter into KwiClick (such as your username and/or password for various services) is stored locally in your browser, not sent to our servers. In order to provide functionality for some services (such as Facebook or Flickr), you may need to enter your username and password for those sites. This information is only transmitted to each respective service, and not to the KwiClick servers.

## 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

### 2.1 Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not share aggregated demographic information about our users with our partners. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. No registration is required to use any of our services.

### 2.2 Personally identifiable information:

We DO NOT Store or Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

## 3\. Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose any information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

### 3.1 Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site and addon, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

### 3.2 Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this website. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but the ability for our service to provide accurate personaliztion for you will be limited. 

### 3.3 Third Party Search Engines

When you execute a query on selected search engines, the KwiClick browser extension makes additional network connections to the search engine and execute additional queries. The additional network connections may cause you to exceed a search engine's bandwidth limit more quickly. The additional search engine queries may affect the search engine's own personalization algorithms.

### 3.4 Third Party Advertisers

The ads that we deliver to users may be provided by our advertising partners. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our advertisements on this site. The information that our advertising partners collect is not personally identifiable.

## 4\. Security

The security of your information is extremely important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [privacy@kwiclick.com](mailto:privacy@kwiclick.com?subject=feedback).

### 4.1 Business Transitions

In the event KwiClick goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any information involved in such transactions and provide notice before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### 4.2 Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## 5\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@kwiclick.com](mailto:privacy@kwiclick.com?subject=feedback).
